export default [
  {
    question: 'In which country is playing "Minecraft" in school allowed?',
    choice1: "Singapore",
    choice2: "Malaysia",
    choice3: "Thailand",
    choice4: "Sweden",
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which real life animal was recorded to produce the sound effects of the Ghasts?",
    choice1: "Cow",
    choice2: "Cat",
    choice3: "Dog",
    choice4: "Sheep",
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "When was Minecraft released?",
    choice1: "15th Jan 2009",
    choice2: "18th November 2011",
    choice3: "27th June 2004",
    choice4: "29th March 2010",
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Which game inspired Notch to create Mincraft?",
    choice1: "Infiniminer",
    choice2: "Mines of Mars",
    choice3: "Adventure Miner",
    choice4: "Deep Miner",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is NOT a Minecraft mod?",
    choice1: "Aether",
    choice2: "Aether II",
    choice3: "Aether II: Reloaded",
    choice4: "Aether II: The Silver City",
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: 'How many people like to play "Minecraft" every month?',
    choice1: "100M+",
    choice2: "55M+",
    choice3: "200M+",
    choice4: "195M+",
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: 'How many night creatures can you find in "Minecraft"?',
    choice1: "10",
    choice2: "3",
    choice3: "7",
    choice4: "5",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "How far away can you be from a Ghast for it to see you?",
    choice1: "30 blocks",
    choice2: "25 blocks",
    choice3: "100 blocks",
    choice4: "50 blocks",
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the best way to kill a Spider in Minecraft?",
    choice1: "With a sword",
    choice2: "With a stick",
    choice3: "With a stick and a spider eye",
    choice4: "With a pickaxe",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Which of these mobs does not drop a item?",
    choice1: "Horse",
    choice2: "Donkey",
    choice3: "Polar Beast",
    choice4: "Silverfish",
    answer: 4,
  },
];
